<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Benchmark xmlns="http://checklists.nist.gov/xccdf/1.2" 
    xmlns:dsig="http://www.w3.org/2000/09/xmldsig#" 
    xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" 
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" 
    xmlns:cpe="http://cpe.mitre.org/language/2.0" 
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:xccdf="http://checklists.nist.gov/xccdf/1.2"
    id="xccdf_RM1_benchmark_org.mitre" xml:lang="en" 
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://checklists.nist.gov/xccdf/1.2 http://scap.nist.gov/schema/xccdf/1.2/xccdf_1.2.xsd">   
    <status date="2013-05-22">incomplete</status>
    <title>XCCDF Plain-text and Sub examples</title>
    <description xml:lang="us">XCCDF Remediation Example for Cisco IOS banner messages.  Based on DISA Network Infrastructure Router STIG.</description>
    <reference href="http://scap.nist.gov/revision/1.2/#xccdf">
        XCCDF: The Extensible configuration Checklist Description Format version 1.2
    </reference>
    <reference href="http://iase.disa.mil/stigs/net_perimeter/network_infra/routers_switches.html">
        DISA Network Infrastructure Router STIG.
    </reference>
    <plain-text id="banner_legalese">You are accessing a U.S. Government (USG) Information System (IS) that is provided 
        for USG-authorized use only. By using this IS (which includes any device attached to this IS), you consent to the following conditions:
        
        -The USG routinely intercepts and monitors communications on this IS for purposes including, but not limited to,
        penetration testing, COMSEC monitoring, network operations and defense, personnel misconduct (PM), law enforcement
        (LE), and counterintelligence (CI) investigations.
        -At any time, the USG may inspect and seize data stored on this IS.
        -Communications using, or data stored on, this IS are not private, are subject to routine monitoring, interception, and search, and may
        be disclosed or used for any USG-authorized purpose.
        -This IS includes security measures (e.g., authentication and access controls) to protect USG interests--not for your personal 
        benefit or privacy.
        -Notwithstanding the above, using this IS does not constitute consent to PM, LE or CI investigative searching or monitoring of 
        the content of privileged communications, or work product, related to personal representation or services by attorneys, 
        psychotherapists, or clergy, and their assistants. Such communications and work product are private and confidential. 
        See User Agreement for details.
    </plain-text>
    
    <version>.1</version>
    <Group id="xccdf_org.mitre_group_2">
        <Rule id="xccdf_org.mitre_rule_ios_banner2" >
            <fixtext fixref="fix_ios_banner" reboot="false" >Enable and configure Cisco IOS with the banner motd command and input the proper legalese 
            </fixtext>
            <fix id="fix_ios_banner" reboot="false" system="urn:xccdf:fix:commands" complexity="low" disruption="low" strategy="configure" platform="cpe:/o:cisco:ios:15.1">
                banner motd ^Banner: Warning you are entering a restricted system.^</fix>
            <fix id="fix_ios_banner1" reboot="false" system="urnxccdf:fix:script:tcl" complexity="low" strategy="configure" disruption="low" platform="cpe:/o:cisco:ios:12.4">banner motd <sub idref="banner_legalese"/></fix>
            <check system="check_ios_banner" id="fix_ios_banner" ></check>
        </Rule>
    </Group>     
</Benchmark>
